chetholmes.com 2007-05-18

# Chet Holmes, Super Strategist of the Fortune 500 Biography

|   
---  
  
****

**See Chet present live**  
  
****  

****  

[ ](http://www.businessgrowthmasters.net/)**[  
Click Here](http://168.144.157.123/)**  
for the most comprehensive small business growth program in the world. I teamed with Jay Abraham to create a no risk, life and business altering program that you must see. And if   
you qualify, a trained business growth consultant of mine will conduct a one hour business growth consultation at no cost or obligation to you.  

Privacy Policy

> Jordon Productions, Inc. ("Company" or "we"), owns and operates the websites located at [www.chetholmes.com](http://www.chetholmes.com/), & [www.chetholmes.info](http://www.chetholmes.info/) The Company delivers advertisements and offers by email to its "list members," that is, people who sign up for offers through our opt-in process via our Site or through one of our many partners' sites. 
> 
> List members can unsubscribe at any time, no questions asked. You can remove yourself from any or all of the lists you signed up for by following the instructions contained in every marketing email sent. Jordan productions bulk commercial e-mail messages sent By Jordan and it's affiliate partners are labeled (though not by a standard method) and include opt-out instructions and the sender's physical address 
> 
> We want our list members to feel comfortable using the Site and participating in the Service and products so we have created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we may collect from you on the Site , through the Service and how we may use that information. Please take a moment to review the terms of our Privacy Policy. By using the Site and participating in the Service or Surveys, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or participate in the Service or Surveys. 
> 
> PERSONAL INFORMATION
> 
> Collection and Use   
>  To simply view the Site without registering for the Service or for the Surveys, you will not be required to provide any personal information. However, to register for the Service or to participate in the Surveys, whether at our Site or at one of our partners' sites, you may be asked to provide your email address. To serve you better and send you the most relevant offers, we may also seek other personally and non-personally identifiable information about you from you, our marketing partners where you have given them your consent, or where such information is otherwise publicly available. Such information may include postal, demographic or transactional information. 
> 
> If you provide us with your email address or other personal information, or if we obtain such information about you from you or from one of our marketing partners, we will retain and use that information solely for the purpose of sending you advertisements, offers and Surveys from selected marketers in categories of interest to you. When necessary, we may also use your personal information to ensure compliance with Company policies and applicable law. 
> 
> In addition, if you participate in a Survey, you will be asked to provide certain information, personal and not, in order for us to determine your suitability for particular Surveys, as certain Surveys may be directed only to those participants who meet a particular demographic profile. You will be asked to answer certain “pre-qualification” questions on a pre-qualification page hosted us by. The information we collect on this page will be used to determine whether you are eligible to participate in the Survey and will also be maintained by us to enable us to provide you with more relevant offers and information in the future. 
> 
> Disclosure of Personal Information   
>  Except for the limited situations discussed in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personal information with any third parties. We may sometimes use other businesses to perform certain services for us that will enable us to send you more relevant offers. In such instances, we may provide your personal information to those businesses but they are not permitted to retain or use your information for any other purpose. **We will not disclose your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.**
> 
> As Company develops, we may buy other businesses or their assets or sell our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that Company or all of its assets are acquired, customer information, including any visitor information collected through the Site or the Service, would be one of the transferred assets. 
> 
> Finally, Company reserves the right to disclose list member information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Company's rights or property, other visitors, list members, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Company also reserves the right to disclose visitor or list member information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 
> 
> AGGREGATE INFORMATION 
> 
> From time to time, we may collect general, non-personal, statistical information about the use of the Site and the Service, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on the Site, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they “click” on. The Company also collects and reports aggregate statistical information on the open rates and response rates generated by the email campaigns we send. We collect this information through the use of technologies such as “cookies” and “IP addresses”, which are discussed in greater detail below. We collect this information in order to determine what types of advertisements are of interest to list members and to therefore enhance the Service. We may also group this information into aggregate visitor data in order to describe the use of the Site and Service to our existing or potential business partners or other third parties, or in response to a government request. However, please be assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you, other list members or any other visitors to the Site. 
> 
> IP Addresses   
>  An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the web. Web servers, the computers that “serve” web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. Company collects IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to third parties and to track the use of the Site. When visitors request pages from the Site or click on a link in a mailing sent through the Service or through our servers log the visitors' IP addresses. We reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify a visitor or list member when it will enhance the users experience or if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the Site's policies or to protect Company, the Site, its visitors, the Service, the list members or others. 
> 
> Cookies   
>  Cookies are pieces of information that a websites transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at the Site. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most websites. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Information such as the total number of visitors and pages viewed is most easily tracked with cookies. We may use the information from cookies to make improvements and updates to the Site and to tailor our services to our visitors', list members' and survey participants' needs. 
> 
> You always have the option of disabling cookies using your browser preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, please be aware that some features of the Site will not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies. 
> 
> LINKS TO OTHER SITES 
> 
> Please be aware that when you are on the Site, or when you receive an email message from us on behalf of a marketer through the Service, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control, such as the marketer's site. And, as discussed above, if you qualify for a Survey on our pre-qualification page, you will be directed to the marketing research company's site. There may be links to other sites from the Site's pages or from the email message we send to you that take you outside our Site. These other sites may send their own cookies to visitors, collect data or solicit personal information. The privacy policies of these other sites may be significantly different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there. 
> 
> SECURITY 
> 
> Protecting the security of your personal information is very important to us. When we store information that you have provided to us when registering for the Service, that information is protected by security measures that include “firewalls” (a combination of computer hardware and software that helps keep unauthorized visitors from accessing information within our computer network), “intrusion detection systems” (a combination of computer hardware and software that helps detect any unauthorized visitors) and other tools such as data encryption and physical security, where appropriate. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data repository can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while Company strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personal information.   
>    
>  PRIVACY POLICY FOR CHILDREN 
> 
> We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 on the Site, through the Service, or through If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide any personal information to us. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. 
> 
> CHANGES TO THESE TERMS 
> 
> The terms of this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting a notice on the homepage of the Site for a reasonable period of time after such changes are made, that this Privacy Policy has been updated, and by changing the “Last Modified” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and participation in the Service or in any Surveys offered through following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 
> 
> QUESTIONS 
> 
> Any questions that you may have regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to [Admin@chetholmes.com](mailto:admin@chetholmes.com)

Free Newsletter | Articles | Research | Bio | Ultimate Sales Manager | Strategic Services  
Free Download | Free Tutorial | Conference Call  | Home

©2002 Jordan Productions. All Rights Reserved No part of this site may be reproduced in any form   
without the specific written permission of Jordan Productions. Web site designed by [Peirson To Peirson](http://www.peirsontopeirson.com/)

|  |   
---  

 For free, you   
can learn how research changes everything.  Would you like to achieve these ten objectives with one single marketing move?

 Would you like to:   
  1) Be positioned as an  
      expert in the eyes of       your clients?

  2) Dramatically upgrade   
       the “influence” you’ll   
       have with your clients?

  3) Show market data that   
       makes having your   
       product more  
       important?

  4) Get people to buy   
        more, more often.

  5) Build information  that   
       positions you   
       strategically above all   
       of your competitors?

  6) Dramatically improve   
       and upgrade the   
       communication  
       experience between you   
       and your prospects? 

  7) Build in a sense of  
       urgency that makes your  
       buyers buy faster? 

  8) Create an unstoppable  
       anti-competitive   
       strategy? 

  9) Breed more loyalty  
       toward you over  
       every other competitor? 

  10) Attract your buyers        over all of your       competitors whenever       they see an ad, a       brochure, a sales letter,        etc…

      Click here to read  
      about Research  
      services…  
  
Recommend this  
site to a Friend
